Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  - Video and Film
    - Oil of Olay (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 79)
      - 177. Olay Hydro-Gel--2 spots (both Sources U.S.). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 79)
    - Oil of Olay (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 80)
      - 179. Beauty Fluid--2 spots (both Promises Renewal w/o 800#). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 80)
      - 180. Renewal Cream--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:15 (Box 80)
      - 181. Daily UV Protectant--Per/35/027/E/T NTSC. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 80)
      - 182. Olay Renewal Cream--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:15 (Box 80)
      - 183. Oil of Olay--Double Jeopardy. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 80)
      - 184. Bath Bar--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 80)
      - 185. Bath Bar--2 spot (Not for air). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 80)
      - 186. Oil of Olay--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 80)
      - 187. Beauty Fluid--2 spots (both Above). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 80)
      - 188. Oil of Olay--2 spots-- (both If). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 80)
      - 189. Oil of Olay--2 spots-- (both Promises Renewal w/o 800#). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 80)
      - 190. Oil of Olay--2 spots. 1993. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 80)
      - 191. Bath Bar--Double Jeopardy Non New Vers. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 80)
      - 192. Beauty Fluid--2 spots (both Promises Renewal w/o 800#). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 80)
      - 193. Bath Bar--Dermatologists Prefer/Rev. 1993. TRT: :15 (Box 80)
      - 194. CF-1--2 spots (both Caring/Lipstick (Photomatic). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 80)
    - Oil of Olay (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 81)
      - 195. Oil of Olay CF-1--2 spots (both Equity). 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 81)
      - 196. Renewal Cream--Numbers Ver. B. 1993. TRT: :37 (Box 81)
      - 197. B-22--Everybody's Talking Rev. 3 (photomatic). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 81)
      - 198. Beauty Fluid--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 81)
      - 199. Olay Bath Bar--She Switched Ver C. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 81)
      - 200. Renewal Cream--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 81)
      - 201. Olay B-22--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 81)
      - 202. Oil of Olay--5 spots (Rip-O-Matic). 1994. TRT: Circa 3:00 (Box 81)
      - 203. Oil of Olay--Lipstick Foundation--3 spots. 1994. TRT: Circa 1:30 (Box 81)
      - 204. Oil of Olay--Everybody's Talking. 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 81)
      - 205. Oil of Olay Renewal Cream--Know Where to Look. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 81)
      - 206. Renewal Cream--Know Where to Look w/Hydroxy. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 81)
      - 207. Olay--Promises--Renewal Puerto Rico (With Mex Demo). 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 81)
      - 209. Olay--Dermatologists Say R/2 CC. 1994. TRT: :15 (Box 81)
      - 210. Beauty Fluid--4 spots. 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 81)
      - 211. Beauty Fluid--Photomatics--3 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 81)
    - Oil of Olay (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 82)
      - 212. Renewal Cream--2 spot (both Know Where to Look). 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 82)
      - 213. Beauty Fluid--8 spots Master. 1994. TRT: Circa 4:00 (Box 82)
      - 214. Beauty Fluid--I Didn't Believe Rev. 3. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 215. Beauty Fluid--Extraordinary Women--Alex Jones. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 216. Beauty Fluid--Notice/ Department Store Revised. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 217. Beauty Fluid Photomatic--Deep Down Rev. 2 Master. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 218. Renewal Cream--4 spots (all Regrets/). 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 82)
      - 219. Oil of Olay SC-23--Dermscan. 1994. TRT: Circa:30 (Box 82)
      - 220. Beauty Fluid--Skin Deep. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 221. Beauty Fluid--NFA. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 222. Oil of Olay Beauty Fluid--Job Interview. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 223. Beauty Fluid--Women Know Swear by It. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
      - 224. Oil of Olay--2 spots Master. 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 82)
      - 225. Oil of Olay--2 spots Master. 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 82)
      - 226. Oil of Olay--Elecator Rev. 1. 1994. TRT: Circa:30 (Box 82)
      - 227. Oil of Olay Renewal Cream--Second Chance Master. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 82)
    - Oil of Olay (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 83)
      - 228. Beauty Fluid--Laugh Rip-O-Matic. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 229. Oil of Olay--2 spots (both Everybody's Talking). 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 83)
      - 230. Oil of Olay--What Women Know, Clock Master. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 231. Women Know--Swears by It. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 232. End Benefit Skin Visualization. 1994. TRT: 8:00 (Box 83)
      - 233. Beauty Fluid--Who are Extraordinary Women Master. 1994. TRT: Circa :30 (Box 83)
      - 234. Oil of Olay Renewal Cream--2 spots (both Guaranteed). 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 83)
      - 235. Bath Bar--Secret Derm / Dr. Ruth. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 236. Moisture Tint--Perfection Rev. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 237. Bath Bar--2 spots (both Secret Derm / Dr.). 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 83)
      - 238. Renewal Cream--2 spots (both Born Again Skin). 1994. TRT: 1:11 (Box 83)
      - 239. Bath Bar--Secret Derm / Dr. Katherine Treherne. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 240. Bath Bar--Down the Drain / Non New. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 241. Beauty Fluid--Right Where I Am Dale. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
      - 242. Renewal Cream--2 spots (both Guaranteed Revised). 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 83)
      - 243. Olay--Fountain of Youth / Barbara. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 83)
    - Oil of Olay (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 84)
      - 246. Bath Bar--2 spots (both Woman Rev.). 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 84)
      - 248. Body Wash--Everybody's Talking. 1994. TRT: :45 (Box 84)
      - 251. Renewal Cream. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 84)
      - 252. Oil of Olay-End Benefit Visualization--8 spots. 1994. TRT: Circa 4:00 (Box 84)
      - 253. Oil of Olay--Moisture Tint Exploratory. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 84)
      - 254. Oil of Olay Sheer Perfection (tint over application shot) - Suzanne Vers. 2 (Final Tested Vers.). 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 84)
      - 255. Renewal Cream--Jullian Johnson Gentle revised. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 84)
      - 256. Renewal Cream--Jullian/Inventor. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 84)
      - 257. Oil of Olay--2 spots; Renewal Cream--4 spots. 1994. TRT: 3:00 (Box 84)
      - 260. Oil of Olay DUVP--Lifetime Jennifer alt. W/ Super. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 84)
      - 261. Creative Brief. Circa 1995. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 84)
      - 281. Foundation--9 spots; Lipstick--4 spots. Circa 1995. TRT: Circa 7:00 (Box 84)
      - No number. Daily Renewal; Protective Renewal; Daily Renewal Cleaner; Revitalizing Eye Gel; Daily Renewal Cream--5 spots. Circa 1995. TRT: Circa 2:30 (Box 84)
      - No number. Oil of Olay--23 spots (list enclosed--no times). Circa 1995. TRT: Circa 12:00 (Box 84)
    - Olympus
      - Misc. 40. Tiegs Bike Race Rev. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 84)
      - Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 84)
    - [Paine, Webber, Jackson, Curtis: see box 86] (Box 84)
    - Pan American Airways (Box 85)
      - 1 Master. Pan Am-- Master Reel #1--34 spots (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0020, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0020.mkv)
      - R-2 Master. Pan Am Master R-2 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0021, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0021.mkv)
      - 3 Master. Pan Am Master Reel 3 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0022, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0022.mkv)
      - 4 Master. Pan Am Master Reel 4 (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: 11:00 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0023, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0023.mkv)
      - 5 Master. Pan Am Master Reel 5 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0024, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0024.mkv)
      - 6 Master. Pan Am Master Reel 6 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0025, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0025.mkv)
      - 48. Pan Am Shuttle--4 spots. 1986. TRT: 2:00 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0026, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0026.mkv)
      - 49. Shuttle--4 spots. 1986. TRT: 2:00 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0027, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0027.mkv)
      - 50. Pan Am--Man-Competition DCA-Rev. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0028, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0028.mkv)
      - 51. Shuttle--4 spots (1986 World Series). 1986. TRT: 2:00 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0029, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0029.mkv)
      - 52. Shuttle--3 spots. 1986. TRT: 2:30 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0030, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0030.mkv)
      - 54. Shuttle--2 spots (both Man-Legroom / Horse) Master. Undated. TRT: 1:00 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0031, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0031.mkv)
      - 54A. Shuttle--Man-Legroom / Horse Master. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0032, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0032.mkv)
      - 55. Shuttle--2 spots (both Man-Have not). 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0033, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0033.mkv)
      - 69. Shuttle--One Hour Meeting Rev. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 85, Video-cassette RL01365-UMATIC-0034, Digital-materials RL01365-SET-0001, Video-file RL01365-UMATIC-0034.mkv)
    - Pepsi
      - Misc. 35. Compilation. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 85)
    - Paine, Webber, Jackson, Curtis (Box 86)
      - 1. Man on Camera. Circa 1975. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 86)
      - 2. Man on Camera (Gag Version). Circa 1975. TRT: 1:00 (Box 86)
      - 3. Organization. 1975. TRT: :50 (Box 86)
    - Phillip Morris
      - #1. Summer Jobs--3 spots. 1983. TRT: 1:10 (Box 86)
      - Misc. 60. Benson Hedge--Disadvantages Rowboat. Undated. TRT: :30 (Box 86)
      - Misc. 62. PM 100's--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:00 (Box 86)
      - Misc. 63. Benson Hedges--2 spots Master (see also box 118--WRG 46 for all commercials? & box 121--WRG 107). Undated. TRT: 2:00 (Box 86)
    - Polaroid
      - 4 spots. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 86)
    - [Pringles: (see boxes 87-95] (Box 86)
    - Purolator Courier
      - 12. Overnight Deliveries--9 spots. 1985. TRT: 4:30 (Box 86)
      - 16. Overnight Delivery--Birds. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 86)
      - Master Reel. Purolator Master Reel (no list). Circa 1985. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 86)
    - Gain (Procter & Gamble) (see boxes 30-32 for more Gain)
      - Gain Show and Smell Challenge--6 spots. 1997. TRT: 3:15 (Box 86)
      - 1A. Gain--7 spots. Undated. TRT: Circa 4:30 (Box 86)
      - Gain--4 spots plus gag spot (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: 1:45+ (Box 86)
      - Gain--22 spots (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 86)
      - Gain--may be same as above. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 86)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (Box 87)
      - R-1. Pringles Master R-1 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 87)
      - 10. Pringles National Advertising--27 spots (list enclosed). 1979. TRT: 16:00 (Box 87)
      - 16. Pringles--4 spots. 1981. TRT: 2:45 (Box 87)
      - 23A. Pringles--Fever / Track Meet. 1981. TRT: :45 (Box 87)
      - 33. Pringles--2 spots (both Models…). 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 87)
      - 34. Pringles--Fever-School Pictures. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 87)
      - 35. Pringles--Fever-School Pictures Rev. I. 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 87)
      - 37. Pringles--2 spots. 1982. TRT: 1:15 (Box 87)
      - 38. Pringles--Chuck McCann--Actor; Non Air Demo Audition; Stan Dragoti--Director. 1982. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 87)
      - 39. Pringles--Michael Pritchard--Actor; Non Air Demo Audition; Stan Dragoti--Director. 1982. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 87)
      - 45. Pringles--Hot Potato/ Rev. (quick & rough). 1982. TRT: :30 (Box 87)
      - 46. Pringles--2 spots (both Saturday Night Fever). 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 87)
      - 47. Pringles--Hot Potato. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 87)
      - 48. Pringles--Hot Potato w/o Idaho. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 87)
      - 49. Pringles Cheez-ums--Twice the Taste (quick & rough). 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 87)
      - 50. Pringles--Big Potato. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 87)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 88)
      - 51. Pringles--2 spots (both Get the Fever). 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
      - 52. Pringles--2 spots (both Airplane). 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
      - 53. Pringles Cheez-ums--The Big Cheese/New. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 54. Pringles--Airplane / Growing Can Rev. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 55. Pringle's Cheez-ums--The Big Cheese / New-Revised. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 56. Pringles-- Models-Silver. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 57. Pringles--Thicker Dipper. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 58. Pringle's Cheez-ums-- The Big Cheese / Non-New. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 59. Pringles Light Potato Chips--Party. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 60. Pringles Light Potato Chips--Lifeguard. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 61. Pringles--3 spots (all Break for Pringles). Circa 1984. TRT: 2:00 (Box 88)
      - 62. Pringles--Catch the Fever. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 63. Pringles Thicker Dipper. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 64. Pringles Rippled Potato Chips--Thicker Dipper. Circa 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 65. Pringles--Movie Madness. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
      - 66. Pringles--Catch the Fever Rev. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 88)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 89)
      - 67. Pringles Cheez-ums--Cheez-ums / Non-New. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 68. Pringles Sour Cream'n'Onion--Dip is in the Chip Rev. 1. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 69. Pringles--Movie Madness / A-Team. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 70. Pringles Sour Cream'n'Onion-- The Dip is in the Chip. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 71. Pringles Sour Cream'n'Onion--1984 Dip is in the Chip Rev. 2. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 72. Movie Madness Rev. I. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 73. Pringles--2 spots (both Movie Madness Hot Potato / Rooftop). 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 89)
      - 74. Pringles--Hot Potato Pool. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 75. Pringles--Return to Oz. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 76. Pringles Sour Cream'n'Onion--2 spots (both The Dip is in the Chip/ Non-New / Rev. 1) Master. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 89)
      - 77. Pringle's Sour Cream'n'Onion--2 spots (both Thicker Dipper / Non-New / Rev. 1) Master. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 89)
      - 78. Pringles Cheez-ums--2 spots (both Cheez-ums Non-New / Rev. 1) Master. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 89)
      - 79. Pringles--Return to Oz Rev. 1. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 80. Pringles--Return to Oz Rev. 2. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 89)
      - 81. Pringles--Beak for Pringles Sliding Tag. 1985. TRT: :45 (Box 89)
      - 82. Pringles Light--2 spots. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 89)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 90)
      - 83. Pringles Potato Chip--Chips. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 84. Pringles--2 spots (both Models-). Circa 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 90)
      - 85. Ripples Potato Chips--Final Gulp. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 86. Pringles Cheez-ums--The Big Cheese/ :15. 1985. TRT: :15 (Box 90)
      - 87. Pringles Cheez-ums--Cheez-ums No-New / Sliding Tag Rev. 2. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 88. Pringles--Tennis Match Reebok. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 89. Pringles SC& O--Dip is in the Chip. 1986. TRT: :15 (Box 90)
      - 90. Pringles--Theatre. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 91. Pringles--2 spots (both The New Big Cheese). 1986. TRT: 1:15 (Box 90)
      - 92. Pringles--The Name's Butter'n'Herbs. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 93. Pringles Light Potato Chips--Tennis Match / Non-Reebok Master. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 94. Pringles--The New Big Cheese Rev. 1. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 95. Light--Tennis Match / Non-Reebok Rev. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 96. Pringles--6 spots. 1987. TRT: 3:00 (Box 90)
      - 97. Pringles--Gymnastics Fever Super. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
      - 98. Pringles Light BBQ Potato Chips--Santa Fe. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 90)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 91)
      - 99. Pringles--3 spots Master. 1987. TRT: Circa 1:30 (Box 91)
      - 100. Pringles--3 spots (same as above). 1987. TRT: Circa 1:30 (Box 91)
      - 101. Chris Hammer. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 91)
      - 102. Pringles--V.O. Transfer. 1987. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 91)
      - 104. Pringles Idaho Ripples--Fasten Your Taste Buds. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 105. Amazing Corn Crisps--Man & Boy. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 106. Amazing Corn Crisps--Amazing Recipe. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 107. Amazing Corn Crisps--Birdie. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 108. Pringles Light Ranch--Country Girls. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 109. Pringles--3 spots (all Camping Rescue). 1988. TRT: 1:45 (Box 91)
      - 110. Pringles Corn Crisps--The Gimmies. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 111. Pringles--2 spots. Circa 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 91)
      - 112. Pringles--Car Revised. Circa 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 113. Pringles Corn Crisps--Silo Rev. Circa 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 114. Pringles Corn Crisps--Silo Rev. 3. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
      - 114A. Pringles Corn crisps--Silo Rev. 3. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 91)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 92)
      - 114A. Pringles Corn crisps--Silo Rev. 3. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 115. Pringles Rippled--Cabin Fever Drink Rev. Circa 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 116. Pringles Light--2 spots (both Flavors). Circa 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 92)
      - 117. Pringles--Once You Pop.. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 119A. Pringles--Pringle Bells Rev. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 120. Pringles Corn Crisps--Health Club. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 121. Pringles--Once You Pop Rev. (Zoom on). 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 121A. Pringles--Once Your Pop Rev. (Zoom on titles). 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 122. Pringles--Build. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 123. Pringles Corn Crisps--More & Less. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 124. Pringles--3 spots. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 125. Pringles Corn Crisps--Cornomonials. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 126. Pringles--2 spots (both Crunch It Up). 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 92)
      - 127. Pringles Corn Crisps--More and Less Rev. 2. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
      - 128. Festiva--Pringles--2 spots (both Conga Line). 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 92)
      - 129. Festiva--Conga Line Alt. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 92)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 93)
      - 130. Pringles Corn Crisps--2 spots (both Conga Line/Alt) Master. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 93)
      - 132. Pringles Corn Crisps--Incredible / Lightomonials. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 133. Pringles--2 spots (both More & Less). 1991. TRT: :45 (Box 93)
      - 134. Pringles--More and Less / Black Can. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 135. Pringles--Fresher Ways. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 136. Pringles Light--2 spots (both Lightomonials Master). 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 93)
      - 137. Pringles--Rhapcity. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 138. Pringles--Rhapcity. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 139. Pringles--Rhapcity Revised. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 140. Pringles Light--Lightomonials Non-New, Rev. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 141. Pringles Dyna Bites--6 milk Demos (list enclosed). 1992. TRT: Circa 3:00 (Box 93)
      - 142. Pringles--2 spots (both Conga Line) Rev. 2 Comp. 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 93)
      - 143. Pringles Light--Lightomonials 2. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 93)
      - 144. Pringle's BBQ--Wild Tang. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 93)
      - 145. Pringle's BBQ--Wild Tang / Lightomonials. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 93)
      - 146. Pringles--2 spots (both Losing It). 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 93)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 94)
      - 148. Pringles-- Fresher Ways Rev. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 149. Pringles--Acapella Yogi. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 150. Pringles--2 spots (both Festivas land). 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 94)
      - 151. Pringles--Rhapcity Rev. 3. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 152. Pringle's--Yogi Rev. 1. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 153. Pringles--Yogi Rev. 2. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 154. Pringles--Fresher Ways Large. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 155. Pringles Sour Cream & Onion--Volleyball. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 156. Pringles--Crunch Happy. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 157. Pringles-- 2 spots (both Crunch Happy). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 94)
      - 158. Pringles Cheez-ums--Kid Rap. Circa 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 159. Pringles--3 spots. Circa 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 94)
      - 160. Pringles--Right Crisps--That's Right. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 161. Pringles--2 spots (both Crunch Happy). 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 94)
      - 162. Pringles--Right Crisps--Light to Right. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 94)
      - 163. Pringles Plus--7 spots. 1994. TRT: 3:30 (Box 94)
    - Pringles (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 95)
      - 166. Pringles--Pringles World Meeting 1994. 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 95)
      - 167. Pringles--3 spots (all Cool / Not Cool). 1994. TRT: Circa 1:30 (Box 95)
      - 168. Pringles--Value Revised. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 95)
      - 168A. Pringles--Value Revised. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 95)
      - 169. Pringles--Tip Song. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 95)
      - 170. Pringles--Crunchious Master. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 95)
      - 171. Pringles--Cool Pop. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 95)
      - 172. Pringles--Value Happy. 1994. TRT: :15 (Box 95)
      - 173. Pringles--Plus Mom. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 95)
      - 174. Pringles Plus--Plus Mom Rev. 1. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 95)
      - 168, 189, 170. Pringles--3 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 95)
      - Pringles--17 spots (list enclosed). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 95)
    - Procter & Gamble: Banner--P& P
      - 1. Banner Master Reel 1. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 95)
      - 2. Banner Master Reel 2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 95)
      - Procter & Gamble Citrus Hill--P& G-- Master reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 95)
      - Procter & Gamble F-97 Coldspot--P& G Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 95)
    - Procter & Gamble: Folgers Coffee- P& G (Box 96)
      - 1. Folgers Gourmet Supreme--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 3:30 (Box 96)
      - 2. Folgers Gourmet Supreme--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 3:30 (Box 96)
      - 3. Folgers Gourmet Supreme Coffee-2 spots (both Club). 1987. TRT: 1:45 (Box 96)
      - 4. Folgers Gourmet Supreme--Wake Up Your Day. 1987. TRT: :45 (Box 96)
      - 5. Folgers Gourmet Supreme--Wake Up Your Day/ Rev. 1. 1987. TRT: :45 (Box 96)
      - 6. Folgers Gourmet Supreme--Wake Up Your Day. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 96)
      - 7. Folgers Gourmet Supreme--Jar Out of Can (Crystal). 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 96)
      - 8. Folgers--Club. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 96)
      - 9. Jar Out of Can. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 96)
      - 10. Folgers Gourmet Supreme--Mountain Site. Circa 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 96)
      - 11. Folgers Gourmet Supreme (Vacuum) --Ship. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 96)
      - 12. Folgers--Club Adventure. Circa 1988. TRT: 2:00 (Box 96)
    - Procter & Gamble: F-90
      - 1. F-90--The Flavor's Big. 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 96)
      - 2. F-90--Ten Feet Tall. 1981. TRT: 1:00 (Box 96)
      - 3. F-90--2 spots Master. 1981. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 96)
    - Procter & Gamble: F-126
      - 4 spots (1. Cornillas; 2. Carambas; 3. Mavericks; 4. Chico, Pepe, Lopez, Rios). 1986. TRT: 2:00 (Box 96)
    - Procter & Gamble: F-123 (Box 97)
      - 2. F-123--Mr. Chunks. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 97)
      - 3. Project Caroline--F123-A & F123-B. 1986. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 97)